Subtitling by DimaTorzok
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the courage
that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there, no regrets.
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
There once was a man
named Mont Blanc Nolan.
He was from a kingdom
in the northern seas.
Nolan, or Nolan the Explorer, always told
stories about his incredible adventures.
They were so incredible that the villagers
could never tell if they were true or not.
One day, Nolan returned from a
long journey to report to the king.
It stands proud and beautiful in ruin.
The city is named Shandora.
But they call it the City of Gold,
which describes it perfectly.
Marie Joie has finally granted us
permission to enter the Grand Line.
So I would like to send
you on another mission.
It would be my pleasure.
There will be a slight change, however.
This time my soldiers
and I will accompany you.
Is that understood?
Yes.
Kalgara!
Seto.
You're off to ring the bell, right?
I'll help you.
It's good to see you too, Noah.
You sure have made yourself at
home in these ruins, haven't you?
Hey, when do you think Noland and
the rest of his crew are coming back?
That's all you ever ask
about when we come here.
It's not exactly easy for him to return.
He was born all the way
in the far northern seas.
He also has a family back
home, but he promised.
As long as we keep ringing
this bell the way we have been,
he'll show up again someday.
What's happened to the sky?
Come on, Shit!
We have to protect the village!
Why?
Why does the island suddenly end here?
Damn you, Noland!
I cannot believe I ever
trusted you, you liar!
Where is the city of gold you
promised I would find here?
Where did the village go?
What happened to the island?
Kalgara, if you're alive,
please ring the golden bell.
Answer me!
Fire of Shandora!
Nolan's public execution
is about to start!
Hey, it's this way, guys!
It's true.
I saw a giant city of gold on
the Grand Line Island of Jaya.
The city of gold does exist, I assure you.
Let us hear from one of your crew.
Is this man telling the truth?
He's not.
It's an absolute lie. No! Please!
You can't trust anything that man says!
He's a liar!
Were all his stories fake?
Hey, that's not fair.
He's been lying to the whole
kingdom and acting like a hero.
Wait, hold on.
Where'd you get that witness?
He's not even a part of our crew.
Did you happen to see Kal
'Gorah and the others?
Commodore, what happened?
Seize all of them.
Damn it!
Leave my men alone.
For his heinous lies, Mount Bronc-Noran
is hereby sentenced to death by beheading.
FIRE!
Liar!
Liar! Liar!
Look at that!
A giant island of birth can you hear
that the singing voice of this beautiful?
Birth it is truly the birth of holy land
this is definitely where I must live!
What's going on here?
what happened?
why can't I breathe?
is everybody all right?
Find yourselves together.
Come on, everyone, get up!
Tend to the wounded!
Hurry!
Kokoro!
I hereby claim this Firth as mine!
You will call me God!
You are not God!
Shandians, we fight!
We cannot let them take our land!
We made a promise, Nolan.
We promised we would meet again someday.
Kal 'gara, where are you?
When you finally return, what will
you think when you see we're gone?
Hold on a little longer.
I'll let you know that we're still here.
Are you alive?
I have so much to tell you.
Kal 'gara, I have to
know if you're alright.
Let's meet again on the same land one day.
Noland!
Light the fire of Shandora!
And the great warrior
Kalgara continued to shout.
Just once would have been enough.
But he believed that the fire of Shandora
would echo and tell the
world that we are here.
But the bell never rang once.
And then everything was
explained to our villagers.
Sailors from the Blue Sea told us
that Noland, to whom we owe so much,
had such pride for our
city that he refused to
deny Shandora's existence
and died known as a liar.
But it was too late.
The great warrior Kal 'gara had died
honorably in battle here in the sky.
He was never able to convey his message,
and that was the Great
Warrior's biggest regret.
Do you think we'd still be able to
reach him if we rang the bell now?
Do you think we'd still
be able to reach Nolan?
Tell me the truth!
That's a good question.
Well, we are close to heaven.
Wiper! Come on!
We'll die if we don't leave now!
Please, Wiper!
Anaru, what gives you the right
to take away everything we know?
This is the sky!
It is God's domain!
Everything is an eyesore!
The people, the trees, the land!
Return to where you belong!
Let everything rain into the Blue Sea!
Get to the boats!
Angel Island won't last much longer!
Sir, what do we do with the
people who've been injured?
Hurry!
We'll treat them once
they're in the boats!
What would have happened if that
girl had approached me any later?
I hope she's alright.
The little angels will scurry
like the ants they are.
Return to where you belong, Skypiea!
What is that?
The hole in the White White Sea!
I have no need for God's
shrine anymore, either.
The city of Shandora is
useless to me as well.
There is only one thing
in this land that I want.
The Gold Belfry.
Suddenly, I hear two voices.
How can he run so fast?
Hang in there, Nami!
I'll take care of this, I promise!
Eneru, I'll never let
you have the Golden Bell!
I don't get it.
What is it that Aniru wants up there?
I believe he's trying to
get to the Golden Bell.
A bell?
A golden bell?
Tell me, that's what you
said, isn't it? Piper? Yes.
But who was talking about a golden bell?
Just before you were struck
by that lightning bolt,
you were speaking of a golden
bell which Eneru desires.
Now that we know what Eneru's going
for, you have to tell me where it is.
Hold on!
Can we just think about
this for one second, guys?
You saw that thunderbolt!
We're as good as dead if
we don't get out of here!
It's up this beanstalk,
somewhere close to the top.
You're sure?
How do you know this?
Wait!
We promised Nami that we'd
wait back on the ship!
She's going to be back with
Luffy any time now, I'm sure!
The coward's right this time!
The ruins of Shandora are in
the lair directly beneath us.
The giant beanstalk pierces
the very center of the city.
Oh man, these ruins or whatever
they are got blasted in dust!
And if we don't get out of here
right now, we're gonna be next!
In the ruins,
I discovered a map that
revealed the location
of the Grand Belfry that
holds the Golden Bell.
It indicated that it could be found
in the heart of the ancient city.
To put it simply,
the force of the impact
with the vine must have sent
the bell hurling skyward
to its present location.
Hey!
The City of Gold's got a
really big bell in it, right?
Finally, I'm above Giant Jack.
Virgin Sky,
I certainly never had reason to come up
here, and I doubt anyone else has either.
Now where is it after 400 years?
It will be found the golden bell
What's with this place
Him.
It would appear that I
underestimated the little rat.
Gotcha!
Stay right there!
Absurd.
Uh, Wiper, what are you planning to do?
Don't tell me you're going
to climb the beanstalk.
Everyone, get away from the beanstalk!
Something's falling!
The top of the stock what's
happening up there oh no don't tell
me Luffy and Nami fell with it
I just don't think I can take it
no you can't go not in
this condition look at
yourself you're a wreck you'd
never make it and even if
you did there's no way
to reach inner while he's
flying on that ship the
bell it's directly above us
Great warrior Kal 'gata
Long to hear its sound
This little predicament will make it very
difficult indeed For you to reach me,
won't it?
You just what?
Hang around a little bit longer
There.
And I'll show you something miraculous.
Show you something?
What is all that?
Oh, yeah.
I guess I should get out of
this while he's not around.
Gum-Gum!
Yo-yo!
What is he doing?
Wow, my plan totally worked, all right
now's my chance to get on board that arc?
Luffy
What are you doing here Nami?
I haven't rescued you yet I came to rescue
you you dold Sanji and Usopp saved me,
so I was safe down below this whole time
Really you were that's great.
I was worried more importantly
What's that?
The thunderclouds!
They're changing shape!
The sky!
Seamus!
Oh no!
Somebody please help us!
The sky!
It's pitch black!
What's happening?
Move it!
Everyone to the sea!
There's a giant ball floating in the sky!
I have a bad feeling about this.
That ball coming through the clouds
over there is a massive thunderhead.
And it's bursting at the seams with
hurricane winds and deadly lightning bolts.
It's right above!
Angel Island!
A thundercloud shaped like a sphere.
Unreal!
This has got to be a nightmare!
What is this?
What new horrors could he unleash next?
Hurry!
Get to the ocean!
Wait for me!
Now everyone will know
that the skies are mine!
With the powers of the Arc Maxim
and myself, I am unstoppable!
I have become truly omnipotent!
Look!
It's falling onto Angel Island!
It's too late!
We're not gonna be dead! HURRY!
EVERYBODY RUN!
Rick!
I don't believe it.
That's impossible.
Did the White Berets escape?
The White Berets saved us all.
The entire island has been destroyed.
Our precious homeland is gone forever.
Even the sea clouds were obliterated.
What a glorious sight to behold.
Now this is what the sky should look like.
What kind of explosion was that?
Not to mention, that terrible lightning
is still falling down like rain.
I don't think any of us stand a
chance of getting out of here alive.
Angel Island's gone.
How could you, Enoru?
What cruelty.
What monstrous cruelty.
What is that rumbling?
We'll wait.
We have to take them back
safely to the Blue Sea.
Luffy get on so we can get back down there
everyone else is headed for the ship and
we should be too i can't why not what are
you saying yeah you can
i don't have to save
you anymore but i still have some unfinished
business unfinished business what's
left to do here are you trying to get back
at inner room that
golden bell is somewhere
up there in the sky you're after the bell
luffy your life is more important than
gold look at that even if the lightning
doesn't hurt you he can still destroy you a
thousand other ways if it's gold you want
you have a load of it on your arm so give
up the bell luffy for your own sake i
won't die will you quit
it already you know?
You saw it, right?
Saw what?
The City of Gold.
You know for a fact it exists, right?
Then it wasn't a lie!
Oldtimer's ancestor.
I don't care if I find the city or not.
I'm not here to prove
Noland right or wrong.
I have no interest in rewriting history.
All I'm doing is following
what I believe is my destiny.
This is between me and Noland.
He wasn't a liar.
I have to let Oldtimer and
the others down below know
that the City of Gold is up in the sky.
If I ring the bell,
Then they should be able to hear it!
Otherwise,
Oldtimer and his monkey pals will keep
searching the ocean floor
until the day they die!
Luffy...
And Aru won't take the Golden Bell!
The sound from a bell that huge will be
heard far and wide by people everywhere!
So I'm not stopping until I hear
the sounds of the Golden Bell!
The City of Gold's got a
really big bell in it, right?
Nolan did mention that
in his logbook, yes.
A great bell in the City of Gold.
Why do you ask, Loopy?
Yeah, why do you ask, Loopy?
I got a really good idea.
Well, tell me.
If we give that ginormous
bell a good ringing,
I bet that old-timer and those monkeys
down below would hear it, don't you think?
Yeah, I bet they would.
When he says that he's gonna
do something, he does it.
Wait!
He's gonna...
Yes, he did say that.
But given the situation...
Ring?
He's going to ring the bell?
That's right.
No matter how hard Nami tries, Luffy
won't leave until he rings that bell.
You see, Luffy is after
the same thing as Eneru.
Got it!
As captain of this ship, I do
not give you permission to board.
HENARU!
Luffy!
See, I told you that was a bad idea!
Damn him!
Wasn't it beautiful?
Did you get to see that pathetic
little island vanish from the sky?
I can only assume that you're
acquainted with how forgiving I am,
especially to those who would deceive me.
Girl, would you still like
a trip to end this birth?
Not a chance!
Once I have finally found the treasured
relic I've been searching for,
I will use another
devastating Rick to annihilate
the rest of this abominable
island in the sky.
Then every inhabitant of Sky Pier
will suffer my terrible wrath!
All will perish, including the
voices directly beneath you.
Beneath us?
I will eradicate this unnatural
land in the sky once and for all.
I will change everything back
to the way it was intended.
That is my sacred duty as an Uru Almighty!
I'm not gonna let that happen!
You won't get away with that!
Your time ends now, Rubber Boy!
Die with dignity!
Luffy!
Face it, it's beyond anyone's
power to stop me now.
Listen, everything will be alright.
I promise, we will send you to the sky.
Luffy...
I'm gonna
ring that bell!
You are just like the moon.
You'll never change as
you climb into the night!
But your reflection waves.
Then you disappear, fading so silently.
Stay as you are, don't lose your way.
Let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams.
There are endless nights that come to you?
All again and again.
Until you see the journey through!
You may not attend.
I hope that you'll learn.
To put your past behind.
And just keep moving on.